where2getit.com 2018-09-18

# Privacy Policy for Location Platform | Brandify

Where 2 Get It, Inc., which does business as Brandify, is committed to working with public policy organizations, industry groups, and government institutions to understand and address privacy issues as they relate to visitors to our Website. This online privacy statement tells you about the information Brandify collects in relation to our website, http://www.brandify.com (the "Website"), how we use that information, and how you can opt out of the uses of your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy or our use of your information, you can email us at [privacy@brandify.com](mailto:privacy@brandify.com). Brandify is located at 222 S. Harbor Blvd., Suite 600, Anaheim, CA 92805.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE USING ANY OF BRANDIFY'S SERVICES DESCRIBED BELOW. BY USING ANY SUCH SERVICES, YOU ARE ACKNOWLEDGING THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS POLICY AND THAT YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ITS TERMS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT, SIMPLY EXIT THIS PAGE WITHOUT ACCESSING OR USING ANY OF OUR SERVICES.

## Information Collection and Use

Brandify collects information in various ways. Those wishing to submit data on Brandify’s Website (“Users”) may submit data expressing interest in products or services advertised on the Website.

Brandify also collects information from third party companies or individuals seeking consumer information or contacts regarding specified goods or services they provide. Brandify collects information from Users by way of questionnaires and/or “Contact Us” forms. This information is submitted voluntarily and is used by third-party clients (“Clients”) to contact the user about the services for which the user has expressed interest.

We may also collect information from third parties or publicly available sources. We may receive personal data about you from various types of third parties, including:

  * Technical Data and/or Tracking Data from analytics providers, advertising networks and search information providers;
  * Identity and Contact Data from data partners; and
  * Data from any third parties who are permitted by law or have your permission to share your personal data with us, such as via social media or review sites.

Brandify may collect and receive Customer data in a variety of ways. When you visit or use our Website or Services in any way, we collect and process different types of information. This information may vary depending on whether you are a Client, or a User of our website. Such information about you may include:

Client Data. Customers or individuals that utilize our services, or those granted access to our services, routinely submit information to Brandify when accessing its services. This data is collecting for the performance of a contract with you. Such information can vary depending on your use of the Website or Services and may include your customers or employees personal data such as:

  * **Identity Data** , including first name, last name, gender, username, email address, employment address, or position;
  * **Contact Data** , including billing address, email address, webpage, or Company information; and
  * **Marketing Data** , including your communication preferences with your Customers, and customer information.

User Data **.** Those using Brandify’s website may be asked to voluntarily submit personal data such as names, addresses, phone numbers, contact information, or email addresses. This information is provided at the consent of the user on behalf of the specified client. 

With respect to Client Data, Brandify acts as a controller of this information. This information is provided for the performance of a contract with our Clients. With respect to User data, Brandify acts as a processor and the Clients are the controllers of such information. With respect to User data, Brandify acts as a processor of such information, on behalf of the controller soliciting such information. Each Controller maintains its individual privacy policy and every User is advised to be familiar with the privacy policy of the entity from whom they solicit information. 

We may, in the future, sell or otherwise transfer some or all of our assets or equity to a third party. Your personally identifiable information and other information we obtain from you via the Website may be disclosed to any potential or actual third party purchasers of such assets or equity and may be among the assets transferred. Any such transfer would ensure a continuation of acceptable privacy policies.

## Privacy of Minors

To access or use the Website, you must be at least 13 years of age, if, under 13 or the age of majority in your jurisdiction, your use must be under the supervision of a parent, guardian, or other responsible adult. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without adult supervision, please contact us at privacy@brandify.com. Any information provided by a child under 13 without parental consent, is subject to removal. 

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive containing information about the user. As part of offering and providing personalized services, we may use cookies to store and sometimes track your information, thereby saving time while you are on our Website. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use the Website; however, the user may be limited in some areas of the Website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Website.

Generally we use cookies to:

  * Access your account information;
  * Track the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Website;
  * Estimate our audience size; and
  * Measure certain traffic patterns.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our Website (e.g., advertisers); however, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

The following cookies are required by our code in order for our store locators to function properly:

  * **W2GISM:** a session cookie which allows us to cache values.
  * **Appkey:** a unique UUID value assigned to a specific locator; one of two ways in which we ensure that the page and resources are loaded and used only by the authorized client.
  * **Authsite:** the URL that has been authorized to use this locator; the second part of our security to ensure the page and resources are used only by the authorized client.
  * **Behavioral targeting:** We may integrate with third party service providers, such as advertising and analytics partners, that use various technologies to collect information, such as cookies, web beacons, or JavaScript, to provide you with personalized content or advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. You may opt out of receiving personalized content or advertisements as described below.
  * **Opting out of cookies and mobile device identifiers:** You may opt out of receiving certain cookies and trackers by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) opt-out page or the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) consumer opt-out page, or by installing the DAA's AppChoice app on your mobile computing device. When you use these opt-out features, an "opt-out" cookie will be placed on your computer, tablet, or mobile computing device indicating that you do not want to receive interest-based advertising from NAI or DAA member companies. If you delete cookies on your computer, tablet, or mobile computing device, you may need to opt out again. You will need to opt out of each browser and device for which you desire to apply these opt-out features.

Data Retention  

Brandify will retain data in accordance with a Customer’s instructions, including any applicable terms in the Customer Agreement, and as required by applicable law. Brandify will retain user information for twelve months following the use of the Website unless the user directs otherwise. Customers or Users may direct the deletion of data at any time. The deletion of Customer or User Data may result in the inability to utilize the website or receive communications from Brandify, or its customers. For more detail, please contact Brandify support. Brandify may retain information following this time period to pursue legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with (and demonstrate compliance with) legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements

Log Files

Every computer connected to the Internet is given an IP address. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and our web servers do not record the email addresses of our visitors.

## Sharing

As a general rule, except as described in this privacy statement, we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances (such as when we believe the law requires it). We may share aggregated demographic information with certain partners, affiliates and advertisers; however, except as described above, this is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell or otherwise disclose or use any and all such aggregated information so long as it is related to the business of the Website. In addition, Brandify may disclose account or other personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with Brandify's rights or property, other Website users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

## International Transfers

Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we will comply with applicable data protection law. This may be accomplished by transferring your data to a country that has officially been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission.

Or, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe (called the “EU Model Clauses”).

## Links

This Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to remain vigilant when they leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Website. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online — for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas — such information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any registration information. Please be careful and responsible when you are online.

Surveys

From time to time our Website may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys, to the extent we run any, is completely voluntary and the user, therefore, has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this Website.

## Security

This Website takes numerous precautions to protect our Users' information. When Users submit sensitive information via the Website, such information is protected both on- and offline. Brandify goes to great lengths to ensure that no unauthorized parties can access information collected during the provision of services through the Website. We encrypt certain sensitive information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that our visitors' information is safe as it is sent over the Internet to our server. SSL works by using a private key to encrypt data that is transferred over the SSL connection. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also take many precautions to protect User information offline. All of our Users' and Clients’ sensitive information is restricted in our offices. While Brandify employs commercially reasonable security measures to protect our data and seeks to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we, therefore, are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

## Site and Service Updates

From time to time we may send our Users and Clients Website and service announcement updates. This communication is to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

## Correcting or Updating Personal Information 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, please send an email to [privacy@brandify.com](mailto:data@brandify.com) or call customer support at 888.377.2767.

## Choice/Opt Out

Our users are given the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving communications from us or allowing us to collect user data at the point where we ask for the information by sending us an email at [privacy@brandify.com](mailto:privacy@brandify.com).

## Rights of EU Citizens (Extended to all Users) 

As a consequence of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) effective May 25, 2018, citizens of the European Union (EU) are granted certain rights related to the collection of personal data by online companies. We hereby extend the rights of EU citizens under GDPR to all users regardless of nationality. Such rights are described below.

The right to be informed – an obligation on Brandify to inform you of the use of your personal data;

The right of access – a right to access personal data we hold about you;

The right to rectification – a right to correct personal data about you that may be incomplete or inaccurate;

The right to be forgotten – in certain circumstances you can ask us to delete the personal data we have about you, unless there is a legal requirement on our part to keep it;

The right to restrict processing – a right for you to request a suspension of personal data processing;

The right to data portability – a right to ask us for a copy of your personal data; and

The right to object – a right for you to object to us with respect to our use of your personal data. 

You may opt out of communications we send you at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link. 

You can object to the processing of your personal information, request portability of your information, or restrict processing of your personal information. Simply contact us at privacy@brandify.com.

If you have previously provided consent for the use of personal information, you may withdraw that consent at any time by contacting us at privacy@brandify.com. 

All communications regarding the exercise of data protection rights are dealt with in an expeditious fashion and in accordance with relevant data protection laws and guidelines. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to archive and store any information that we deem reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

In order to make any of the above requests, or if you have any concerns regarding data use or privacy, please send an email to [privacy@brandify.com](mailto:privacy@brandify.com).

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes under the appropriate link on the home page of our Website, so our Users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for periodically reviewing this privacy statement to apprise yourself of any changes. If at any point, we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from what was stated at the time it was collected, we will notify Users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy statement under which the information was collected.

Brandify does not respond to Do Not Track signals or other mechanisms that provide consumer choice about tracking.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding any issue relating to our privacy practices, you may contact us using the information below.

Where2GetIt, Inc. dba Brandify  
222 S. Harbor Blvd  
Suite 600  
Anaheim, CA 92805  
Attn: Privacy Manager   
Email: [privacy@brandify.com](mailto:privacy@brandify.com)   
Telephone: 888-377-2767
